We build sales teams for companies just shy of 14 million this year, we'd like to be at 100 million.
We've done the math. The amount of leadership and fulfillment we would need for those clients
wouldn't be profitable. You likely do have a pricing issue. The eventuality of all service-based
businesses, especially B2B, is that the price continues to go up and that's the way it works
because you chase bigger and bigger customers, you charge bigger and bigger premiums, and that
is the virtuous cycle of services. You always have a supply constraint if you're in services,
if you're good. And because of that, you increase your price and then you're able to get more
A players in because you can afford them, which increases your reputation, increases demand,
which allows you to get more A players, and so you go from paying $100,000 people to $250,000
to a million dollar a year people to multi-million dollar per year people. That's where it goes.